Guide to the Rick Lazio Papers, 1981–2005
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IV. Press Coverage
  - Press Clippings
    - 8-13 Mar 2000 (Box 128)
    - 14-16 Mar 2000 (Box 128)
    - 17-20 Mar 2000 (Box 128)
    - 21 Mar 2000 (Box 128)
    - 23 Mar 2000 (Box 128)
    - 24-27 Mar 2000 (Box 128)
    - 28-30 Mar 2000 (Box 128)
    - 30-31 Mar 2000 (Box 129)
    - Apr 2000 (Box 129)
    - 10-11 May 2000 (Box 129)
    - 12-16 May 2000 (Box 129)
    - 17-18 May 2000 (Box 129)
    - 22 May 2000 (Box 129)
    - 23 May 2000 (Box 129)
    - 24-25 May 2000 (Box 129)
    - 26-30 May 2000 (Box 129)
    - 31 May 2000 (Box 129)
    - Jun 1-2 2000 (Box 130)
    - Jun 5-6 2000 (Box 130)
    - Jun 7-8 2000 (Box 130)
    - Jun 9 2000 (Box 130)
    - Jun 12 2000 (Box 130)
    - Jun 13-14 2000 (Box 130)
    - Jun 15-16 2000 (Box 130)
    - Jun 19-20 2000 (Box 130)
    - Jun 21-22 2000 (Box 131)
    - Jun 23 2000 (Box 131)
    - Jun 25-26 2000 (Box 131)
    - Jun 27-28 2000 (Box 131)
    - Jun 29-30 2000 (Box 131)
    - Jul 2-5 2000 (Box 131)
    - Jul 6-7 2000 (Box 131)
    - Jul 10-11 2000 (Box 131)
    - Jul 12-13 2000 (Box 131)
    - Jul 14-17 2000 (Box 132)
    - Jul 17-18 2000 (Box 132)
    - Jul 19-20 2000 (Box 132)
    - Jul 21-24 2000 (Box 132)
    - Jul 25-26 2000 (Box 132)
    - Jul 27-28 2000 (Box 132)
    - Jul 31 2000 (Box 132)
    - Aug 1-2 2000 (Box 132)
    - Aug 3-4 2000 (Box 133)
    - Aug 6-7 2000 (Box 133)
    - Aug 8 2000 (Box 133)
    - Aug 9-11 2000 (Box 133)
    - Aug 12-14 2000, (2 folders) (Box 133)
    - Aug 15 2000 (Box 133)
    - Aug 16 2000 (Box 134)
    - Aug 17 2000 (Box 134)
    - Aug 18 2000 (Box 134)
    - Aug 19-20 2000 (Box 134)
    - Aug 21 2000 (Box 134)
    - Aug 22 2000 (Box 134)
    - Aug 23-25 2000 (Box 134)
    - Aug 26-27 2000 (Box 134)
    - Aug 28 2000 (Box 135)
    - Aug 29-30 2000 (Box 135)
    - Aug 31-Sep 1 2000 (Box 135)
    - Sep 2-3 2000 (Box 135)
    - Sep 4-5 2000 (Box 135)
    - Sep 6-7 2000 (Box 135)
    - Sep 8 2000 (Box 135)
    - Sep 9-10 2000 (Box 136)
    - Sep 11 2000 (Box 136)
    - Sep 12 2000 (Box 136)
    - Sep 13 2000 (Box 136)
    - Sep 14 2000, (2 folders) (Box 136)
    - Sep 15 2000 (Box 136)
    - Sep 16-17 2000 (Box 136)
    - Sep 18 2000 (Box 137)
    - Sep 19-20 2000 (Box 137)
    - Sep 21 2000 (Box 137)
    - Sep 22 2000 (Box 137)
    - Sep 23 2000 (Box 137)
    - Sep 25-26 2000 (Box 137)
    - Sep 27-30 2000 (Box 137)
    - Oct 1-2 2000 (Box 138)
    - Oct 3-4 2000 (Box 138)
    - Oct 5-6 2000 (Box 138)
    - Oct 7-9 2000 (Box 138)
    - Oct 10-11 2000 (Box 138)
    - Oct 11-13 2000 (Box 138)
    - Oct 14-16 2000 (Box 138)
    - Oct 17-18 2000 (Box 138)
    - Oct 19-20 2000 (Box 138)
    - Oct 21-22 2000 (Box 139)
    - Oct 23-24 2000 (Box 139)
    - Oct 25 2000 (Box 139)
    - Oct 26-27 2000 (Box 139)
    - Oct 28-31 2000 (Box 139)
    - Nov 1-2 2000 (Box 139)
    - Nov 3-7 2000 (Box 139)
    - Nov 13 2000 (Box 139)
    - Jun 2 2000 (Box 143)
    - Jun 3-5 2000 (Box 143)
    - Jun 6 2000 (Box 143)
    - Jun 7 2000 (Box 143)
    - Jun 8 2000 (Box 143)
    - Jun 9 2000 (Box 143)
    - Jun 12 2000 (Box 143)
    - Jun 13-14 2000 (Box 143)
    - Jun 15 2000 (Box 143)
    - Jun 16 2000 (Box 144)
    - Jun 19-20 2000 (Box 144)
    - Jun 21 2000 (Box 144)
    - Jun 22 2000 (Box 144)
    - Jun 23-24 2000 (Box 144)
    - Jun 25-26 2000 (Box 144)
    - Jun 27 2000 (Box 144)
    - Jun 28 2000 (Box 144)
    - Jun 29 2000 (Box 145)
    - Jun 30 2000-Jul 1 2000 (Box 145)
    - Jul 4-5 2000 (Box 145)
    - Jul 6 2000 (Box 145)
    - Jul 7 2000 (Box 145)
    - Jul 8-9 2000 (Box 145)
    - Jul 10 2000 (Box 145)
    - Jul 11 2000 (Box 145)
    - Jul 12 2000 (Box 146)
    - Jul 13 2000 (Box 146)
    - Jul 14 2000 (Box 146)
    - Jul 15-16 2000 (Box 146)
    - Jul 17 2000 (Box 146)
    - Jul 18 2000, (2 folders) (Box 146)
    - Jul 19 2000 (Box 146)
    - Jul 20 2000 (Box 147)
    - Jul 21 2000 (Box 147)
    - Jul 22-23 2000 (Box 147)
    - Jul 24 2000 (Box 147)
    - Jul 25 2000 (Box 147)
    - Jul 26 2000 (Box 147)
    - Jul 27 2000 (Box 147)
    - Jul 28 2000 (Box 148)
    - Jul 29-30 2000 (Box 148)
    - Jul 31 2000 (Box 148)
    - Aug 1 2000 (Box 148)
    - Aug 2 2000 (Box 148)
    - Aug 3 2000 (Box 148)
    - Aug 4-5 2000 (Box 148)
    - undated, (newsprint) (Box 149 (Oversize))
    - Jan 1991-Nov 1992, (newsprint) (Box 149 (Oversize))
    - Mar 1993-Jul 1993, (newsprint) (Box 149 (Oversize))
    - Aug-Dec 1993, (newsprint) (Box 149 (Oversize))
    - Jan-Apr 1994, (newsprint) (Box 149 (Oversize))
    - May-Aug 1994, (newsprint) (Box 149 (Oversize))
    - Sep-Dec 1994, (newsprint) (Box 149 (Oversize))
    - Jan-Apr 1995, (newsprint) (Box 149 (Oversize))
    - May-Aug 1995, (newsprint) (Box 149 (Oversize))
    - Sep-Dec 1995, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - 1996, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - 1997, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - 1998, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - Newsday – Jan-Dec 1998, (2 folders, newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - Jan-Apr 1999, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - May-Jul 1999, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - Aug-Dec 1999, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - Jan-May 2000, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - 4-17 May 2000, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - May 20-21 2000, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - May 22-23 2000, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - May 24 2000, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - May 25 2000, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - May 26-27 2000, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - May 28-29 2000, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - May 30-31 2000, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - Jan-2 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - 3-4 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 5-6 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 7-8 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 9-10 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 11-12 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 13-14 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 15-16 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 16-17 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 19-20 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 21-22 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 23-25 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 26-27 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 28-29 Jun 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - 30 Jun 2000-1 Jul 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Jul 3-4 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Jul 5-6 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Jul 7-8 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Jul 9-10 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Jul 11-12 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Jul 13-14 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Jul 15-16 2000, (newsprint) (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Jul 17-18 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Jul 19-20 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Jul 21-22 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Jul 23-24 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Jul 25-26 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Jul 27-28 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Jul 29-30 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Jul 31 2000-Aug 1 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Aug 2-3 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Aug 4-5 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Aug 6-7 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Aug 8 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Aug 9-10 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Aug 11-12 2000, (newsprint) (Box 152 (Oversize))
    - Aug 13-14 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Aug 15-16 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Aug 17-18 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Aug 19-20 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Aug 21-22 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Aug 23-24 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Aug 25-26 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Aug 27-28 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Aug 29-30 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Aug 31 2000-Sep 1 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Sep 2-3 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Sep 4-5 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Sep 7-8 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Sep 8-9 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Sep 10-11 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Sep 12-13 2000, (newsprint) (Box 153 (Oversize))
    - Sep 14-15 2000, (newsprint) (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - Sep 16-17 2000, (newsprint) (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - Sep 18-19 2000, (newsprint) (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - Sep 20-21 2000, (newsprint) (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - Sep 22-23 2000, (newsprint) (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - Sep 23 2000, (newsprint) (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - Sep 25-28 2000, (newsprint) (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - Sep 29 2000-Oct 2 2000, (newsprint) (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - Oct 3-6 2000, (newsprint) (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - Oct 7-10 2000, (newsprint) (Box 154 (Oversize))
    - Oct 11-14 2000, (newsprint) (Box 155 (Oversize))
    - Oct 15-18 2000, (newsprint) (Box 155 (Oversize))
    - Oct 19-22 2000, (newsprint) (Box 155 (Oversize))
    - Oct 23-26 2000, (newsprint) (Box 155 (Oversize))
    - Oct 27-30 2000, (newsprint) (Box 155 (Oversize))
    - Oct 31 2000-Nov 2 2000, (newsprint) (Box 155 (Oversize))
    - Nov 2 2000-Nov 3 2000, (newsprint) (Box 155 (Oversize))
    - Nov 4-7 2000, (newsprint) (Box 155 (Oversize))
    - Oct 2 2005 (Box 155 (Oversize))
    - Dec 27 1990-Jan 23 2000, (large newsprint) (Box 156 (Oversize))
    - May 20 2000-Jun 5 2000, (large newsprint) (Box 156 (Oversize))
    - Jun 9 2000-Jul 9 2000, (large newsprint) (Box 156 (Oversize))
    - Jul 14 2000-Sep 23 2000, (large newsprint) (Box 156 (Oversize))
    - Oct 1 2000-Nov 22 2000, (large newsprint) (Box 156 (Oversize))
    - Miscellaneous full issues of magazine with Lazio pieces or references, Jul-Nov 2000; (3 folders) (Box 162)
  - Press Releases
    - Mar-Oct 1996 (Box 140)
    - Jan-Dec 1997 (Box 140)
    - Jan-Dec 1998 (Box 140)
    - Jan-Dec 1999 (Box 140)
    - Feb-12 2000 (Box 140)
    - Mar-Jun 1993 (Box 141)
    - Jul-Dec 1993 (Box 141)
    - Jan-Jun 1994 (Box 141)
    - Jul-Dec 1994 (Box 141)
    - Jan-May 1995 (Box 141)
    - Jun-Dec 1995 (Box 141)
    - Jan-Jun 1996 (Box 142)
    - Jul-Dec 1996 (Box 142)
    - Jan-Jun 1997 (Box 142)
    - Jul-Dec 1997 (Box 142)
    - Jan-Oct 1998 (Box 142)
- Series V. Printed Material
  - Pre-Congressional
    - Campaign Against Tom Downey (flyers produced by Citizens to Save the 2nd Congressional District), 1991 (Box 158)
  - Pre-Congressional/Congressional
    - Campaign Flyers, Brochures, Mailers, 1991-1996 (Box 156 (Oversize))
    - Campaign Announcements, Mailers, Flyers, 1991-2000 (Box 109)
    - Campaign Flyers, Posters, Brochures, 1991-2000 (Box 151 (Oversize))
  - Congressional Papers
    - Campaign Bumper Stickers, 1992-2000 (Box 158)
    - Rick Lazio Newsletters - Citizen Reports, 1993-1996 (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Voting Record Report, Dec 1993-Dec 1999; (newsprint) (Box 156 (Oversize))
    - Newsletters with mentions of Rick Lazio (Columbia University, American Cancer Society, Housing Management Quarterly, Vassar College, Lazio Report from Congress,etc.), 1993-2000; (3 folders) (Boxes 109, 151 (Oversize))
    - Lazio Congressional Letterhead, undated (Box 109)
  - Congressional/Senate Campaign Papers
    - Campaign Baseball Cards, Postcards, Sample Donation Forms, Lazio stickers, Brochures, 1995-2000 (Box 109)
    - Lazio for Senate Bubble Gum packaging, Lazio hand fan, 2000 (Box 158)
    - Lazio Senate Campaign Advertisements, 2000; (newsprint) (Box 156 (Oversize))
- Series VI. Audio-Visual
  - Lazio ’92, undated; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - Congressional Forum, 19 Mar 1993; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - 1993 NAB PSAs, Patricia Lazio: Breast Cancer, Prostate Cancer, Drunk Driving, undated; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - News 12 – Somalia, Health Bill, H.S. Press Conference, Health Care Conference, 27 Jan - 4 Feb 1994; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - Rick Lazio, Health Care Forum at AIL Systems Inc., 30 Aug 1994; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - Hillary/Mario ’94, undated; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - The New Majority Dinner Video, "Monday Morning", NRCC, 26 Jan 1995; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - NRCC "100 Day" Video, Contract Celebration, 7 Apr 1995; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - Contract With America Celebration, 7 Apr 1995; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - AARP Reverse Mortgages, R.L. Guest Speaker, 15 Aug 1995; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - Television broadcast, WLIG-TV 55, "Focus," Rep. Rick Lazio, 27 Nov 1995; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - Television broadcast, WLIG-TV 55, "Focus," (12/3/95), News 12, At Issue, View from the Hill, family pressures, Reps: Wolf and Roemer, 3-28 Dec 1995; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - Our Lady Of Consolation Ground Breaking, 8 Dec 1995; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - Lazio Fundraiser, 9 Dec 1995; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - Lazio Fundraiser, 9 Dec 1995; (Video-VHS) (Box 1)
  - Television broadcast, View from the Hill, Rep. Nancy Johnson, Medicare, View from the Hill, RL with local reporters, Eyewitness News conference, RL on Presidential Primary WLIG, Cutting Edge, re: Itzhak Rubin, 16 Nov 1995 - 3 Mar 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - Television broadcast, WLIG-TV 55, The Cutting Edge (3/1/96), Republican Nomination, RL Guest, 1 Mar 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - Fannie Mae/House New York, Info From Various News Stations, 4 Mar 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - Hon. Rick Lazio – One Minute Statement Regarding Police Officer Kevin Gillespie, 20 Mar 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - Television broadcast, C-SPAN Bus Bignette, Rep. Rick Lazio, RL interview, 28 Mar 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - Television broadcast, Crossfire, misc., 25 Apr 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - Television broadcast, View from the Hill with Rep. John Kasich, H.S. Press Conference WLIG-TV 55, RL with students, Crossfire – Housing – RL Cisneros, View from the Hill with Senior Advocates, 4 Apr-2 May 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - R.L. – Jim Lehrer News Hour On Housing with …, 8 May 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - House Floor Debate On Housing, Tape I, 8 May 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - U.S. House of Representatives Floor Coverage, 9 May 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - Lazio on CNN, 15 May 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - Power, Politics and You, 3 Jun 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - Congressman Rick Lazio: Celebration Dinner, NSSC Conference, 15 Jul 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - WLIG-TV 55, The Cutting Edge, The Republican Congress, Rick Lazio as Guest, 19 Jul 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - Courthouse Groundbreaking, 22 Jul 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 2)
  - Power, Politics and You Election Night Special, Smithtown Sheraton, Rick Lazio, 5 Nov 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - WLNY – TV 55, Focus with R.L. as Guest, 20 Dec 1996; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - CBS Campaign ’96 Abortion Topic, R.L. Interviewed, undated; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - Lazio Debate ’96 News 12, News 12 Report on R.L. Campaign, News 2 Sunday/R.L., View From Hill/R.L., undated; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - Lazio for Congress ’96 Television Highlights, undated; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - Lazio for Congress ’96 Television Highlights, undated; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - NRCC "Revolution" One Year to Victory, Campaign ’96, undated; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - Murray/Weitzner Group Demo Reel 1996, undated; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - WLNY – TV 55 Focus – Congressman Rick Lazio, 14 Feb 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - Focus, 14 Feb 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - Sunday Edition: Rick Lazio and Peter King Discuss Various Issues (i.e. abortion, campaign finance, etc.), 4 Apr 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - Rep. Forbes With Guest Rick Lazio: The Congressman and the Community, The Government and Long Island Through the Eyes of the Congressman, 9 Apr 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - Capitol Watch, 22 Apr 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - RL House Floor Debate Day 1 and Day 2, part 1, 30 Apr-1 May 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - RL House Floor Debate Day 2, part 2, 1 May 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 3)
  - RL House Floor Debate Day 3, 6 May 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - RL House Floor Debate Day 4 and Day 5, 7-8 May 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - Sunday Edition, Rick Lazio on Juvenile Crime Bill, Tax Cuts, etc., 9 May 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - RL House Floor Debate Day 6, Day 7, Day 8, 8-14 May 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - RL House Floor Debate Day 8 Conclusion, 14 May 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - RL’s National Response to the President – National Radio Address, CNN Headline News, May 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - Rep. Rick Lazio "Great Housing Debate" Message for NAHMA, 20 Jun 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - News 12 – Fire Island, Floor Statement on Egypt, Jul 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - WLNY – TV 55 Focus: Labor Issues With Guest Rick Lazio, 29 Aug 1997; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - Bay Shore Summit 1998 (not played at summit, RL chose to appear, 3 Feb 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - RL In the Speaker’s Chair, 25 Feb 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - House Floor – Homeless Bill, 3 Mar 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - NBC – Jay DeDapper Senate 2000 Speculation, Channel 55, Gunther Tax Event, 5 Mar 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - Rep. Rick Lazio – A View From the Hill, Guests Rep. Richard K. Armey and Rep. J. Billy Tauzin, 19 Mar 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - Cancer Fighting Forum – Good Samaritan Hospital, 6 Apr 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 4)
  - RL Face Off, 1 Jul 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - RL Face Off, 9 Jul 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - National Cable Television Association: "TV Smarts For Kids", Congressman Lazio, 4 Aug 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - Lazio – Floor On Public Housing, 6 Oct 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - Long Island Impeachment Coverage, Teddy Roosevelt Coverage – News 12, 7 Oct 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - Lazio For Congress Approval Pub., 12 Oct 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - WLNY – TV 55 News Live at 11, Reporter Pete Palamero, Story: Yankee Games, 2 Nov 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - Fox News Sunday, 8 Nov 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - WCBS Sunday Edition, 15 Nov 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - Crier Report – Fox – GOP Leadership, 18 Nov 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - ABC News – World News Tonight, 8 Dec 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - Lazio on NBC’s "Today" Re: Impeach, 9 Dec 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - CNN, 9 Dec 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - CNN – Special On Impeachment, 10 Dec 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - CNN – Late Edition, 13 Dec 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 5)
  - RL – Rep. Sisisky, Wolf Blitzer Interview from Jerusalem on Clinton Impeachment, 13 Dec 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - Lazio – House Floor Speech – Impeach Vote, 18 Dec 1998; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - Video on the Library of Congress Bicentennial 1800-2000, 21 Jan 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - CBS News, 12 Apr 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - WLNY – TV 55, Topic: Senate Race, 28 May 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - Lazio Clips (delay announce), 11 Aug 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - "Michael Long" Eyewitness News WCBS-TV New York, 22 Aug 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - WLNY-TV 55, News 55 Focus, Topic: Tax Bill, Elections, Guests: Rep. Rick Lazio, 17 Sep 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - WLNY-TV 55, News 55 Focus, Topic: Tax Bill, Elections, Guests: Rep. Rick Lazio, 17 Sep 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - Work Incentives Improvement Act, Wartime Violations Act Floor Debate, 19 Oct-10 Nov 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - CSPAN "Washington Journal", Work Incentives, other issues, 10 Nov 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - CNN "Late Edition", Larry King Live, MSNBC – Crosstalk, 14-29 Nov 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - AIDS/ Workforce, CBS Weekend News, Adams/Zolbag, 27 Nov 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - WLNY-TV 55, News 55 Focus, Topic: Housing and Pres. Elec., Guests: Rep. Rick Lazio, 10 Dec 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - WLNY-TV 55, News 55 Focus, Topic: Housing and Pres. Elec., Guests: Rep. Rick Lazio, 10 Dec 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - Congressman Rick Lazio rings the NYSE Opening Bell, 13 Dec 1999; (Video-VHS) (Box 6)
  - Lazio On ABC "This Week", undated; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - Larry King Live, 17 Jan 2000, 7 Feb 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - Fox News Channel, 7 Feb 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - Fox News Channel – G.W. Bush, MSNBC Equal Time – G.W. Bush, Minimum Wage Floor Statement, 7-9 Mar 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - Utica News in Upstate Swing, 24 May 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - Conversation with Hillary Clinton, 25 May 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - TV Commercial – "Introduction" Lazio For Senate 2000, 1 Jun 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - TV Commercial – "Guess What" Lazio For Senate 2000, 18 Jun 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - Pressman, Little Falls, NY, 7 Jul 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - NBC News 5 and11 O’clock, 13 Jul 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - TV Commercial – "Know" Lazio For Senate 2000, 13 Jul 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - Comcast Convention Moments, Rep. Rick Lazio, 21 Jul 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - Mideast Peace Talk Conclusion, Pres. Clinton, 25 Jul 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - WSTM News "Senator Schumer Supports Gov. Pataki on Job Growth Statistics,", 2 Aug 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - WSTM News "Senator Schumer Supports Gov. Pataki on Job Growth Statistics,", 2 Aug 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 7)
  - TV Commercial – "Get Real" Lazio For Senate 2000, 11 Aug 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - TV Commercial – "Effective" Lazio For Senate 2000, 17 Aug 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - "Lazio For Senate" Eyewitness News WABC-TV New York, 21 Aug 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - "Senate Race" Eyewitness News WABC-TV New York, 23 Aug 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - TV Commercial – "Positive" Lazio For Senate 2000, 24 Aug 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - TV Commercial – "Trust" Lazio For Senate 2000, 28 Aug 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - TV Commercial – "Believe" Lazio For Senate 2000, 29 Aug 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - TV Commercial – "Ringer" Lazio For Senate 2000, 1 Sep 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - TV Commercial – "Plan" Lazio For Senate 2000, 10 Sep 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - TV Commercial – "Double" Lazio For Senate 2000, 10 Sep 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - TV Commercial – "On The Issues" Lazio For Senate 2000, 18 Sep 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - TV Commercial – "Create" Lazio For Senate 2000, 20 Sep 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - "Rick Lazio" Channel 2 News Saturday WCBS-TV New York, News 4 New York at 11WNBC-TV New York, 23 Sep 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - "This Week" with Sam Donaldson and Cokie Roberts, 24 Sep 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 8)
  - TV Commercial – "Pataki" Lazio For Senate 2000, 28 Sep 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - TV Commercial – "Bill RNC" Lazio For Senate 2000, 28 Sep 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - TV Commercial – "Bill" Lazio For Senate 2000, 29 Sep 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - Meet the Press – Lazio, 1 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - Eyewitness News – Up Close, Schuner/Muzzio, 1 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - TV Commercial – "Skaneateles R" Lazio For Senate 2000, 9 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - TV Commercial – "Education" Lazio For Senate 2000, 9 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - TV Commercial – "Field" Lazio For Senate 2000, 13 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - TV Commercial – "Beach" Lazio For Senate 2000, 13 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - Lazio in Kingston, NY, 14 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - TV Commercial – "Apple" Lazio For Senate 2000, 16 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - TV Commercial – "Pear" Lazio For Senate 2000, 18 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - TV Commercial – "Peach" Lazio For Senate 2000, 20 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - TV Commercial – "Emerald" Lazio For Senate 2000, 20 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 9)
  - TV Commercial – "Banana" Lazio For Senate 2000, 23 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 10)
  - TV Commercial – "Our Friend" Lazio For Senate 2000, 27 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 10)
  - TV Commercial – "DeFransisco Lazio For Senate 2000, 27 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 10)
  - TV Commercial – "Giambra" Lazio For Senate 2000, 27 Oct 2000; (Video-VHS) (Box 10)